He was really found
It's the one from Lu Group
Mr. Fu from that meeting the other day
Isn't he that bodyguard from the wedding banquet
A bodyguard? Have you ever seen one expose
a funding gap in just a few words
Starting today
Fu Chenzhou officially resumes
his status as the Fu family heir
Meanwhile his marriage to Ms. Su Mingyao
is recognized and respected by the Fu family
Chairman, Mr. Fu just returned to the Fu family
does his marriage
need further evaluation
Evaluate what
He chose his wife himself
The first thing the Fu family should do isn't questioning
but respecting his choice
Everyone in Nancheng laughed at Su Mingyao for marrying a bodyguard
Who's laughing now
Sure enough
Fu Chenzhou really is the Fu family heir
No wonder
Gu Chengze got a huge slap in the face
The pain doesn't matter
Starting today
if the Gu family wants to treat him like an ordinary bodyguard
that's impossible now
Lin Yao, is this real